

# STAN KRIVTSOV

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+33 766 83 67 29

Paris, France

in linkedin.com/in/sdkrivtsov

Pf www.krivtsoff.me

### OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated and seasoned individual with a proactive approach. Transitioned from 9 years of project management and business analysis to become an IT developer. Successfully completed the comprehensive Common Core education program at École 42. Specializing in web development with a focus on frontend, Next.js & ReactJS.

#### LANGUAGES

• English: fluent

• Russian: native speaker

• French: beginner level

• German: beginner level

### SKILLS

- Functional programming
- Teamwork player
- Adaptability, learnability

#### STACK

- JS / TS, HTML, CSS
- React, Next.js, Node.js
- C / C++
- Git
- Unix
- Docker, Kubernetes

### HOBBIES

- Football, cycling, climbing
- Video gaming

# EDUCATION

### WEB AND MOBILE DEVELOPMENT, RNCP 7 (Bac+5)

École 42 / Association 42

2021 - present | Paris

#### PROJECT MANAGEMENT, MASTER'S

National Research University "Higher School of Economics"

2009 - 2011 | Moscow

### STRATEGIC MANAGEMENT, BACHELOR'S

National Research University "Higher School of Economics" 2005 - 2009 | Moscow



42

# RELATED EXPERIENCE

#### FULL-STACK DEVELOPER | Internship

QuantCube Technology | Sept 2023 - present | Paris

- Stack: Typescript, Javascript, ReactJS, Next.js, Node.js, Docker, UNIX.
- Responsible for:
  - 1. Visualization of the real-time platform of Big Data indicators;
  - 2. Design and development of new pages and features on the platform;
  - 3. Mock-ups and integration of Dataviz interfaces and interactive dashboards;
  - 4. Specification of technical and ergonomic improvement.

#### C++ DEVELOPER

École 42 projects | 2022 (about 500 hours)

- Stack: C++, HTTP, Makefile, Algorithms, Git, Kubernetes.
- Implementation of an HTTP server in C++ 98: https://github.com/jesuisstan/42\_http\_webserver
- Implementation of C++98 standard template library container types, such as Vector, Map, Set and Stack: https://github.com/jesuisstan/42\_stl\_containers

#### C Lang DEVELOPER

École 42 projects | 2021 (about 300 hours)

- Stack: C lang, Makefile, UNIX, Git, Multithreading.
- Implementation of Shell (bash) in C language including main builtins, redirections and pipe:

https://github.com/jesuisstan/42\_minishell

• Simulation of the "Dining Philosophers Problem" using processes, mutexes and semaphores:

https://github.com/jesuisstan/42\_philosophers

# OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

#### ANALYST IN BUSINESS EFFICIENCY DEP.

OJSC "Russian Railways" | 2016 – 2020 | Moscow

#### PROJECT MANAGER IN NETWORK DEVELOPMENT DEP.

PJSC "VimpelCom" (VEON Russia) | 2014 – 2015 | St.Petersburg

#### **EXTERNAL AUDITOR**

LLC "Ernst & Young" | 2011 - 2013 | Yekaterinburg